picturesun.top 2018-11-10

# » Privacy Policy • Index of Online Schools

This privacy policy sets out what kind of information we collect, how we use and safeguard the information that you give when you use this site. We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.

What We Collect & How We Use

As is true of many other sites, we collect information automatically and store it in order to understand and serve our customers better. The information we get involves the following:

I. Personally Identifiable Information  
This site gathers personal information voluntarily submitted by visitors, such as names, postal addresses and email addresses etc. The information you provide will only be used to fulfill your specific request and facilitate your browsing through our website. Unless we get your permission, we will never use your personal information for other purpose and will never deliver you newsletter, promotional emails or market research questionnaires.

II. Cookie  
We may use cookie and tracking technology to gather information including browser type, operating system, IP address and number of visitors, aiming to understand our visitors’ preferences and provide better and more efficient customer services in the future.

Notice that your personal information, except what you choose to share with us, cannot be collected via cookies or any tracking technology. But aggregate cookie and tracking information may be used by third parties who advertise on our website.

Google uses cookies to serve ads on our site. As a third party vendor, its use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads based on users visit to websites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. You can disable cookies through your browser options if you like.

Commitment to Security

Your privacy is of huge importance to us and we endeavor to ensure the security of your information. We may have to share information with government agencies for fraud prevention or investigation, but will never sell or lease it to others. Customers who have previously agreed to receive emails or newsletters from us are allowed to opt out of further mailings at any time.

Change of Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes will take effect immediately after being posted.
